Guide to the International Brigades Archive, Moscow: Selected Images ALBA.PHOTO.177
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Folder 196: Album of 15th International Brigade Photographed by Yugoslavian Volunteer, Major Vladimir Stefanovich (None Identified), Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937
  - [Open countryside, telephone pole to the right], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196089)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/89
  - [Bushes, mountains barely visible in far distance], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196090)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/90
  - [Farmer with wide-brimmed hat], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196091)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/91
  - [Mules hitched up to wagon], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196092)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/92
  - [Man with rifle standing in field], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196093)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/93
  - [Man riding a mule. Duplicate of 177_196117], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196094)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/94
  - [Open countryside, mountains in distance], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196095)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/95
  - [Mountainous countryside], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196096)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/96
  - [Rugged countryside], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196097)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/97
  - [Trees line the horizon with mountain behind], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196098)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/98
  - [Car driving along twisty mountain road with tunnel], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196099)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/99
  - [Palm trees along side of road], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196100)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/100
  - [Church tower over looking other buildings], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196101)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/101
  - [Crowd walking the street of a town], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196102)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/102
  - [Officers gathered in town], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196103)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/103
  - [Two officers talking with two women], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196104)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/104
  - [Officers looking at a letter], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196105)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/105
  - [Officers sitting in wicker chairs], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196106)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/106
  - [High shot cars and trucks in town], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196107)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/107
  - [Older man with beret sitting in a chair], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196108)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/108
  - [Man at typewriter in communications post], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196109)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/109
  - [Three men pose among buildings], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196110)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/110
  - [Horse-drawn cart on road], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196111)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/111
  - [Several carts being pulled by horses], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196112)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/112
  - [Man walking beside horse-drawn wagon], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196113)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/113
  - [Horse pulling a covered wagon], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196114)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/114
  - [Horse hitched to wagon, another grazing at roadside], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196115)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/115
  - [Farmer with wide-brimmed hat], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196116)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/116
  - [Man riding a mule. Duplicate of 177_96094], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196117)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/117
  - [Man with rifle standing in field], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196118)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/118
  - [Food preparation, men eating], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196119)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/119
  - [Group of children], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196120)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/120
  - [People washing at public fountain], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196121)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/121
  - [Children with buckets at fountain], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196122)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/122
  - [Unloading gear from the back of a truck], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196123)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/123
  - [Officer and troops in town], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196124)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/124
  - [Troops march through town], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196125)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/125
  - [Officers pose with women overlooking countryside], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196126)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/126
  - [Mountains rising from tree-dotted land], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196127)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/127
  - [Barren open field], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196128)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/128
  - [Two officers seated, talking], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196129)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/129
  - [High shot barren land], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196130)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/130
  - [Soldiers congregating in trench], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196131)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/131
  - [Men socializing outdoors], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196132)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/132
  - [Three shirtless men, one with head/eye bandage, sit and talk], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196133)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/133
  - [Men talking outside sandbag shelter], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196134)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/134
  - [Rugged countryside. Man leaning on rifle in background], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196135)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/135
  - [Wide shot group of men in field], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196136)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/136
  - [Men in trench, one aiming rifle], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196137)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/137
  - [Two men opening a small barrel], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196138)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/138
  - [Soldier arranges papers on a board], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196139)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/139
  - [Soldier holding a newspaper outside of a shelter], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196140)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/140
  - [Soldier making repairs to a jacket], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196141)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/141
  - [Soldier sewing while others look on], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196142)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/142
  - [Rock formations jutting out from hillside], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196143)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/143
  - [Forked tree], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196144)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/144
  - [Tank on rocky terrain], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196145)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/145
  - [Caves in the rock], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196146)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/146
  - [Armed soldiers pose in trench], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196147)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/147
  - [Large gathering of men near trees], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196148)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/148
  - [Two soldiers pose seated together], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196149)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/149
  - [Group shot posed in a trench], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196150)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/150
  - [Palm trees near a town], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196151)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/151
  - [Village visible in the distance], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196152)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/152
  - [Town buildings visible over tops of palm trees], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196153)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/153
  - [Edge of town], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196154)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/154
  - [Buildings built against rocky cliff in distance], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196155)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/155
  - [Aquaduct leading into town], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196156)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/156
  - [Building on rocky hillside], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196157)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/157
  - [Buildings along coastline], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196158)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/158
  - [Rock wall in field], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196159)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/159
  - [Tank near a small tree], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196160)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/160
  - [Large truck and men on dirt path], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196161)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/161
  - [Trucks parked near camp/trench site (?)], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196162)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/162
  - [Men on horseback], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196163)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/163
  - [People piling into and on top of bus], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196164)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/164
  - [Woman walking through fields carrying a basket on her head], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196165)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/165
  - [Men on horseback], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196166)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/166
  - [Seated soldier poses with rifle], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196167)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/167
  - [Officers among group of soldiers], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196168)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/168
  - [Troops resting in front of shelter], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196169)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/169
  - [Men sit with rifles in a trench], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196170)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/170
  - [High shot of the countryside with river], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196171)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/171
  - [High shot of the countryside with river and hillside], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196172)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/172
  - [High shot river winding across the land], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196173)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/173
  - [High shot river winding across the land], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196174)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/174
  - [Group pose officers], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196175)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/175
  - [Officers meeting outdoors], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196176)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/176
  - [Men sit on a bench along ivy-covered wall], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196177)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/177
  - [Small group of men gathered outdoors], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196178)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/178
  - [Small trees dot countryside], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196179)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/179
  - [Barren terrain], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196180)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/180
  - [High shot open land], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196181)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/181
  - [Men digging out trench/foxhole visible on barren hillside], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196182)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/182
  - [Low angle tank], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196183)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/183
  - [Men inside sandbag shelter, one reading a book], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196184)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/184
  - [Shadows inside dug-out shelter], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196185)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/185
  - [Shadows inside dug-out shelter, man sitting inside writing], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196186)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/186
  - [African-American soldier poses on stone wall], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196187)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/187
  - [Soldier in beret next to tree], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196188)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/188
  - [Two men sit on ground next to each other], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196189)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/189
  - [Two men sit on stone wall next to each other], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196190)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/190
  - [Group shot in trench next to a tree], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196191)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/191
  - [Men inside sandbag shelter, man on left reads a book], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196192)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/192
  - [Soldiers walking in trench], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196193)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/193
  - [Four men carry a large piece of lumber (?)], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196194)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/194
  - [Truck with full bed driving. Man stands in back of trucks with goods], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196203)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/203
  - [Man and boy with mules in field], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196204)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/204
  - [Men sitting in an improvised shelter], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196205)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/205
  - [Low angle man with wide-brimmed hat], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196206)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/206
  - [People visible atop wall in background. Men also in foreground], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196207)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/207
  - [Men in a public square], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196208)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/208
  - [People gather near a truck], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196209)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/209
  - [A group of children], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196210)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/210
  - [Rocky cliffs], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196211)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/211
  - [High shot overlooking the countryside], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196212)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/212
  - [Rock formation above open plain], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196213)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/213
  - [Mountainous terrain], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196214)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/214
  - [River running through open plain], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196215)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/215
  - [Mountainous countryside], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196216)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/216
  - [Wide open plains], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196217)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/217
  - [Hilly countryside], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196218)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/218
  - [Trees and bushes], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196219)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/219
  - [Man and mule with pack], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196220)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/220
  - [Bushes and small trees. Railroad tracks (?)], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196221)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/221
  - [Men riding mules along the side of a road], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196222)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/222
  - [Plowing a field with two mules], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196223)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/223
  - [Plowing a field with two mules], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196224)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/224
  - [Plowing a field with two mules], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196225)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/225
  - [Mules carrying goods along a roadside], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196226)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/226
  - [Riverbank with shady trees], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196227)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/227
  - [Man standing in the middle of a dirt road], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196228)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/228
  - [Donkeys eat next to a building in town], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196229)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/229
  - [A donkey], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196230)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/230
  - [Plowing a field with two mules], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196231)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/231
  - [Two mules], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196232)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/232
  - [Men resting among small bushes], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196233)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/233
  - [Plowing a field with two mules], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196234)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/234
  - [Dense vegetation], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196235)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/235
  - [Open fields with cypress (?) trees], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196236)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/236
  - [Dense vegetation], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196237)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/237
  - [Ruins of a large building], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196238)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/238
  - [More ruins in a field], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196239)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/239
  - [Railroad tracks passing by a small settlement], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196240)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/240
  - [Cypress trees, mountains in background], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196241)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/241
  - [Cypress trees, mountains in background], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196242)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/242
  - [Women walking down a path from a house], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196243)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/243
  - [Arched trellis with vines growing on it], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196244)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/244
  - [People washing and bathing in a river], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196245)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/245
  - [A small child wearing sandals], Feb 11, 1937-Mar 7, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 22, Item 177_196246)
    Moscow Number: 5/196/246
- Folder 197: Album of 15th International Brigade Presented to the American Communist Volunteers of the 15th Brigade by the Communist Party of Spain (Postcards, Drawings, and Signatures), Oct 1938
  - [Three-pointed logo of the International Brigades], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197001)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/1
  - [Josef Stalin], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197002)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/2
  - [Stalin quotation], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197003)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/3
  - [Jose Diaz], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197004)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/4
  - [Jose Diaz quotation], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197005)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/5
  - [Dolores Ibarruri], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197006)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/6
  - [Slogan], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197007)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/7
  - [Dimitrov], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197008)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/8
  - [Dimitrov quotation], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197009)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/9
  - [Andre Marty and Comisario Gallo], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197010)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/10
  - [Drawing: "Quedaremos Siempre Hermanos"], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197011)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/11
  - [Earl Browder], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197012)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/12
  - [Browder quotation], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197013)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/13
  - [Spanish Communist Party manifesto], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197014)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/14
  - [Spanish Communist Party manifesto], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197015)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/15
  - [Spanish Communist Party manifesto], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197016)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/16
  - [Spanish Communist Party manifesto], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197017)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/17
  - [Drawing: railroad through mountains, ocean liner], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197018)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/18
  - [Signatures], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197019)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/19
  - [James Ford quotation], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197020)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/20
  - [Wlliam Z. Foster quotation], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197021)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/21
  - [Drawing: man's face and cityscape], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197022)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/22
  - [Drawing: soldiers with rifles and bayonets; list of battles], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197023)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/23
  - [List of names], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197024)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/24
  - [List of names], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197025)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/25
  - [List of names], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197026)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/26
  - [List of names], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197027)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/27
  - [List of names], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197028)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/28
  - [Latin American Communist statement], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197029)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/29
  - [List of names], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197030)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/30
  - [William Z. Foster], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197031)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/31
  - [Cover of album, inscribed from the Communist Party of Spain to the American Communists of the Fifteenth International Brigade], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197032)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/32
  - [Drawing: soldier saluting huge fist with hammer & sickle], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197033)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/33
  - [Group photo of American communist of the Fifteenth International Brigade], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197034)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/34
  - [James Ford], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197035)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/35
  - [Drawing: "Communist International" with various flags], Oct 1938 (Box 2, Folder 23, Item 177_197036)
    Moscow Number: 5/197/36